<?xml version="1.0" encoding="UTF-8"?>
<deals>
	<fromDisplayName>OES</fromDisplayName>
	<fromEmailAddress>oestesting@hotmail.com</fromEmailAddress>
	<promoHeading>MATTRESSES</promoHeading>
	<promoSubHeading>FREE BOX SPRING</promoSubHeading>
	<promoDescription>Applies to select merchandise.</promoDescription>
	<promoSubDescription>Discount applied when ordering.</promoSubDescription>
	<promoCode>NONE</promoCode>
	<promoExpiryDate>03/06/2016</promoExpiryDate>
	<shopNowLink>http://www1.macys.com/shop/mattress/beautyrest-mattress?id=30764&amp;edge=hybrid</shopNowLink>
	<savingsPassLink>http://www1.macys.com/cms/deals/MOTHERS_DAY_Sale_15percent_off_W3040188wis?LinkType=Homepage&amp;cm_mmc=OpsEmail-_-offer_share-_-savingspass-_-MB</savingsPassLink>
	<promoLegalDisclaimer>*To get extra savings, place qualifying items in shopping bag. Discount taken off regular, sale and clearance prices, with exclusions listed. EXCLUDES: 7 For All Mankind, Beats by Dr. Dre, Birkenstock, Born, Chantelle, Coach, CW-X, Denim &amp; Supply Ralph Lauren, Donald J Pliner, Donatella, Dr. Martens, Ecco, Ed Hardy, Goddess, Joe's Jeans, Lacoste, Levi's®, Merrell, Minnetonka Moccasin, Ralph Lauren Childrenswear, Sofft, The North Face, Tretorn, Va Bien, men's &amp; women's athletic footwear, baby gear, kids'shoes, toys, cosmetics &amp; fragrances, sunglasses, Sunglass Hut, select fashion jewelry &amp; watches, Gift Cards. FOR HER: Anita lingerie, bridge &amp; designer handbags, B.Tempt'd by Wacoal, Calvin Klein lingerie, DKNY lingerie, Dolce Vita, Felina, Impulse clothing, Jezebel, Lauren Ralph Lauren, Le Mystere, Lunaire, MICHAEL Michael Kors, Naturalizer, Not Your Daughter's Jeans, Sperry Top-Sider, select Steve Madden shoes, Wacoal. FOR HIM: Armani Jeans, Asics, Cole Haan, Dockers®, Emporio Armani, Hugo Boss, Johnston &amp; Murphy, Marmot, New Balance, Polo Ralph Lauren, Spyder, Tommy Bahama, Tumi. FOR THE HOME: All-Clad, J.A. Henckels, Le Creuset, Tempur-Pedic, Tumi, Wusthof, electrics &amp; electronics, furniture, mattresses, rugs, regular-priced china, silver &amp; crystal. Savings do not apply to Everyday Values, jewelry specials, Jewelry Super Buys, Specials, web busters™, purchases in Macy's stores or prior purchases, payments on credit accounts, gift wrap or shipping charges.</promoLegalDisclaimer>
</deals>
